#### TUSHAR MILIND KATAKDOUND (1) Featured



Sr. Mobile Application Lead seeking roles in Product Management, Android Development, Requirement Gathering, Project Management, Technical Architecture, Application Programming, Software Development, Mobile Application Development, JIRA, MySQL, Linux, Core Java



Current Designation: Assistant Product Manager Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 9 Month(s)

Current Company: TikMe Mobile Technologies Pvt Ltd Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: B.Sc [Computer Science]

Pref. Location: Ahmedabad, Mumbai, Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Product Management, Sr. Mobile Application Lead, Software Developer, Android Development, Requirement

Gathering, Project Management, Technical Architecture, Application Programming, Software Development, Mobile

Application Development, JIRA, MySQL, Linu

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

### Summary

2 Years Of experience in Product Management

Created Wireframe in Figma, Adobe Xd, Zeplin,

Creating Projecting requirement document (PRD).

Sprint Planning in Jira, and conducting daily stand-up, sprint retrospective, & backlog discussion

Skilled and efficient Android Developer with 5+ years of experience creating unique and modern applications available in the Google Play Store.

Product Management, Tech Team Management, Direct interaction & co-ordination with client & investor of app.

Good knowledge of interaction with web service APIs.

Published 10+ Android applications on Google Play Store.

## Work Experience

TikMe Mobile Technologies Pvt Ltd as Assistant Product Manager May 2020 to Till Date

GaintView Technologies Pvt Ltd. as Senior Android Developer Mar 2019 to May 2020

In Gaintview I am working as a Product Manager as well as Sr. Android Developer

Conchact Mobile LLP as Android Developer - Project Lead Oct 2016 to Feb 2019

Appsplanet Technology Pvt Ltd as Android Developer Oct 2015 to Oct 2016

Bytelogica Solution as Freelancer Apr 2015 to Oct 2015

**Vgantaram Technology Pvt Ltd.,** as Android Developer Oct 2014 to Apr 2015

#### **Education**

UG: B.Sc (Computer Science) from Pune University in 2015

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Android, Core Java			
Node.js			
Sqlite, MySql			
REST APIs			
Android Studio, Eclipse			
Photoshop, Sketch			
Linux, Windows, Mac OS			
Flutter		0	0 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

# **Languages Known**

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
Marathi	Expert			
Hindi	Proficient			

### **Affirmative Action**

**Work Authorization** 

Category: SC

Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No

Employment Status: Full time